Byungwoo Jeon

50, Sinchon-ro 28-gil, Seoul, Republic of Korea

📱+82 10 33641362 | 🗷 ipcs@korea.ac.kr | 🛠 rootyjeon.github.io/ | 🖸 github.com/rootyJeon | 🛅 linkedin.com/in/byungwoo-jeon

Research Interest

My research goal is to build a comprehensive system of visual recognition and generation beyond the human level. To this end, I focus on (i) how to extend cognitive abilities using generative models, (ii) how to ensure prior knowledge and temporal consistency using representations of foundation models, and (iii) how to develop a robust alignment of visual and language semantics under novel tasks.

- Self-supervised Learning
- Multi-modal Representation
- · Generative Models
- Neural Rendering

Education

Korea University Seoul, Korea

B.S. in Computer Science & Engineering, Statistics (Double Major)

Mar 2020 - Aug 2024 (Expected)

Experience

Algorithmic Intelligence Lab (ALINLAB), KAIST AI

Undergraduate Intern (advisor: Prof. Jinwoo Shin)

- · Researched Self-supervised Learning and Zero-shot Adaptation of Vision-Language Models
- · Researched Depth Estimation with Neural Radiance Fields
- Participated in the ALINLAB weekly group paper study (Paper reading & Implementation)

ARCREAL Gangnam, Korea

Research Intern (host: Prof. Jinwoo Shin)

Jan 2023 - Current

- · Developed AI systems for medical equipment
- Developed segmentation projects • Researched several 3d vision topics

Machine Learning & Vision Lab (MLVLAB), Korea Univ. CSE

Undergraduate Intern (advisor: Prof. Hyunwoo J. Kim)

- · Studied Open-Vocabulary Object Detection
- Studied Human-Object Interaction (HOI)
- Participated in the government policy supporting AI challenge team
- Participated in the MLVLAB weekly group paper study (Paper reading & Implementation)

M-Monstar Pangyo, Korea

Full-stack Developer

• Developed a modular e-commerce management platform page using Laravel framework

· Optimized and debugged the site, HAGO

Jeongja, Korea

Anam, Korea

Jul 2022 - Dec 2022

Jul 2021 - Aug 2021

Mar 2023 - Current

MARCH 2, 2024

Honors & Awards

K-Data Science HackathonSiheung, Korea

Second-Place $(2^{th}/200)$

- Award by the chairman of Korea Research Foundation, Prize 3,000,000 won
- Developed a multi-stage time-series forecasting model for predicting school-age population

Artificial Intelligence Grand Challenge

Seoul, Korea

Oct 2022 - Dec 2022

- Developed AI for supporting the government policies based on natural language proceessing
- · Developed query parser for pre-processing

Training

Top 9 (8^{th} Prize)

United Collegiate Programming Contest

Seoul, Korea

3 Problems solved

Jul 2021

Yonsei-NAVER CLOUD Data Science Course

Seoul, Korea

Completed financial engineering course

Feb 2021 - Jun 2021

Skills.

Programming Python (PyTorch, TensorFlow), C, C++, SQL, PHP, Javascript, R, SAS

Miscellaneous Linux, Firebase, Git, MEX

Soft Skills Teamwork, Problem-solving, Documentation, Engaging Presentation.

Extracurricular Activity

KUBIG

Member Jul 2023 - Jan 2024

- · Lectured Mathematics and Statistics for Deep Learning
- Developed personalized animated-video service using diffusion models
- Participated in Computer Vision and Time Series Seminar
- Participated in Stochastic Optimization Session (2024 Winter) of Professor Sungbin Lim, Korea Univ.
- · Participated as a pacemaker in Deep Learning Session (2023 Summer) of Professor Sungbin Lim, Korea Univ.

Google Developer Student Clubs

Lead & Founder Jul 2022 - Aug 2023

- Lectured Machine Learning, Databases, and Algorithm courses for undergraduate students
- Developed stable diffusion crawling with text summarization project
- Developed Horang-Studio, personalized AI profile service using diffusion models
- Developed 2024 Google Solution Challenge project (Recovery)
- Developed 2023 Google Solution Challenge project (digiHow)
- Lead three teams to the Global Top 100 in 2023 Google Solution Challenge
- Lead one team to the Global Top 10 in 2023 Google Solution Challenge
- · Host of 2023 East Asia GDSC Global Hackathon in Tokyo

Korea Computer Science Academy (Academy club in Korea Univ.)

Member & Instructor Mar 2022 - Mar 2022

- Lectured Data Structure course for undergraduate students
- Lectured C Programming course for undergraduate students

Languages_

English Professional proficiency
Korean Native proficiency

MARCH 2, 2024 2

Coursework_

2020-1	Fundamentals of Data Science	
2020-2	Computer Programming	
2020-2	Probability and Statistics	
2020-2	Data Structure	
2021-1	Algorithm	
2021-1	Theory of Computation	
2021-1	Discrete Mathematics	
2021-1	Linear Algebra	
2021-2	Databases	A+, Second-place
2021-2	Computer Network	
2021-2	Computer Architecture	
2022-1	Statistical Mathematics	
2022-1	Introduction to Probability Theory	
2022-1	Operating Systems	
2022-1	Artificial Intelligence	A+
2022-2	Machine Learning	A+
2022-2	Deep Learning	A+
2022-2	Regression Analysis	
2022-2	Mathematical Statistics	
2022-2	Probability and Random Process	
2023-1	Analysis	
2023-1	Natural Language Processing	A+
2023-1	Computer Vision	A+
2023-1	Statistical Data Science	A+, First-place
2023-2	Numerical Analysis	A+
2023-2	Introduction to Bayesian Statistics	A+
2024-1	Multivariate Statistical Analysis	
2024-1	Advanced Machine Learning	

March 2, 2024 3